ROBERT ISAAC CORTEZ NURSING – UTS

G01/10 Stockyard Boulevard, Lidcombe NSW 2141 isaacebitacortez@gmail.com 0434524008

BRIEF OVERVIEW

I am a 2nd year university student enrolled in a nursing course in University of Technology Sydney. I am interested in working part-time during my study. I am a good researcher, communicator, and listener. I am also willing to learn more so that I can be a better professional in my field. I look forward to being a part of a positive work culture with passionate people.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SECRETARY/PERSONAL ASSISTANT

BLUE DRAGON - SOUTH COTABATO, PHILIPPINES

April 2018 to February 2019

Served as the Secretary/Personal Assistant to the CEO of Blue Dragon

CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE

BLUE DRAGON - SOUTH COTABATO, PHILIPPINES

April 2018 to February 2019

Served as the Customer Service Representative of Blue Dragon

STUDENT NURSE

BANKSTOWN-LIDCOMBE HOSPITAL

Bankstown, New South Wales, Australia

December 2020 (2 weeks)

February 2021 (2 weeks)

Served as a Student Nurse in Bankstown-Lidcombe Hospital

CROYDON COMMUNITY - MENTAL HEALTH CENTRE

Croydon, New South Wales

April 2021 (2 weeks)

Served as a Student Nurse in Bankstown-Lidcombe Hospital

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN NURSING

UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY SYDNEY - SYDNEY NSW

March 2020 to Present

FOUNDATION DEGREE (PATHWAY TO UNIVERSITY)

UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY SYDNEY - COLLEGE - SYDNEY NSW

March 2019 to January 2020

HIGH SCHOOL (YEAR 12)

NOTRE DAME OF MARBEL UNIVERSITY - SOUTH COTABATO

June 2017 to March 2018

SKILLS

- MICROSOFT OFFICE (10+ YEARS)
- ADOBE PHOTOSHOP (LESS THAN I YEAR)
- LEADERSHIP (9 YEARS)
- RESEARCH (5 YEARS)
- CREATIVE WRITING (10+ YEARS)
- ESSAY WRITING (10+ YEARS)
- CUSTOMER SERVICE (2 YEARS)
- DATA ENTRY (7 YEARS)
- SALES (LESS THAN I YEAR)
- GUITAR (10+ YEARS)